<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<beans xmlns="http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans"
 xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
 xmlns:context="http://www.springframework.org/schema/context"
 xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans/spring-beans-3.0.xsd
  http://www.springframework.org/schema/context http://www.springframework.org/schema/context/spring-context-3.0.xsd">

 <!-- Scans the classpath of this application for annotated beans starting at this point -->
 <context:component-scan base-package="jsr250annotations" />
 
 
	<bean id="match1" class="com.captaindebug.producerconsumer.Match">
		<constructor-arg value="Fulham vs Manchester United" />
        <constructor-arg>
            <list>
<value>95:30 END OF FILE</value>
<value>95:00 Final Score  Fulham 0 - 1 Man Utd</value>
<value>94:59 Full time The referee signals the end of the game.</value> 
<value>90:00 +3:52 Unfair challenge on Mladen Petric by Danny Welbeck results in a free kick. Shot comes in from Hugo Rodallega from the free kick.</value> 
<value>92:07 David De Gea restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>92:07 Booking Wayne Rooney shown a yellow card. </value>
<value>91:56 Patrice Evra fouled by Damien Duff, the ref awards a free kick.</value>
<value>90:43 Urby Emanuelson takes a shot. Rio Ferdinand gets a block in. John Arne Riise takes the outswinging corner, Philippe Senderos takes a shot. Robin van Persie makes a clearance.</value> 
<value>89:39 Unfair challenge on Philippe Senderos by Javier Hernandez results in a free kick. Free kick taken by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>89:04 Mladen Petric gives away a free kick for an unfair challenge on Michael Carrick. Direct free kick taken by David De Gea. 87:53 Bryan Ruiz takes a shot. Wayne Rooney gets a block in. 84:32 Urby Emanuelson challenges Javier Hernandez unfairly and gives away a free kick. Free kick crossed by Ryan Giggs, clearance by Sascha Riether.</value> 
<value>83:09 Mark Schwarzer takes the indirect free kick.</value> 
<value>83:09 Substitution Danny Welbeck is brought on as a substitute for Luis Nani.</value> 
<value>83:09 The offside flag is raised against Robin van Persie.</value>
<value>80:55 Substitution Mladen Petric on for Ashkan Dejagah. 80:55 Outswinging corner taken left-footed by Damien Duff from the left by-line, Hugo Rodallega has a headed effort at goal from deep inside the area missing to the left of the target.</value> 
<value>78:09 Assist on the goal came from Jonny Evans.</value> 
<value>78:09 Goal - Wayne Rooney - Fulham 0 - 1 Man Utd Wayne Rooney fires in a goal from the edge of the area to the bottom right corner of the goal. Fulham 0-1 Man Utd.</value> 
<value>78:09 The assist for the goal came from Jonny Evans.</value> 
<value>78:09 Goal scored - Wayne Rooney - Fulham 0 - 1 Man Utd Wayne Rooney grabs a goal from the edge of the penalty box to the bottom right corner of the goal. Fulham 0-1 Man Utd.</value> 
<value>76:38 Free kick awarded for a foul by Jonny Evans on Bryan Ruiz. John Arne Riise restarts play with the free kick, Chris Baird produces a right-footed shot from outside the penalty box and misses right.</value> 
<value>75:54 Outswinging corner taken left-footed by Damien Duff, Chris Baird takes a shot. Clearance by Rafael Da Silva. </value> 
<value>74:19 Substitution Ryan Giggs is brought on as a substitute for Tom Cleverley. </value> 
<value>72:19 Header by Ashkan Dejagah from deep inside the penalty area misses to the left of the target. </value> 
<value>70:54 Sascha Riether takes a shot. Save by David De Gea. </value> 
<value>68:58 Inswinging corner taken left-footed by Robin van Persie from the right by-line, clearance by Chris Baird. </value> 
<value>66:47 Free kick crossed right-footed by Luis Nani from right channel, John Arne Riise makes a clearance. </value> 
<value>66:47 Substitution Urby Emanuelson is brought on as a substitute for Giorgos Karagounis. </value> 
<value>66:47 Free kick awarded for an unfair challenge on Robin van Persie by Chris Baird. </value> 
<value>64:44 Shot comes in from Robin van Persie from the free kick, comfortable save by Mark Schwarzer.</value> 
<value>64:44 Substitution Javier Hernandez comes on in place of Antonio Valencia. </value>
<value>64:44 Booking for Chris Baird. </value>
<value>64:40 Chris Baird challenges Antonio Valencia unfairly and gives away a free kick. </value>
<value>63:33 Luis Nani takes a shot. Philippe Senderos gets a block in. Inswinging corner taken by Wayne Rooney from the left by-line, Bryan Ruiz manages to make a clearance. </value>
<value>62:29 The assistant referee flags for offside against Luis Nani. Indirect free kick taken by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>62:13 Shot from 25 yards from Chris Baird. Save by David De Gea. </value>
<value>60:40 Rafael Da Silva concedes a free kick for a foul on Bryan Ruiz. Giorgos Karagounis takes the direct free kick. </value>
<value>59:51 Hugo Rodallega is ruled offside. Rio Ferdinand restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>57:59 Robin van Persie is ruled offside. Indirect free kick taken by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>55:47 Effort on goal by Rafael Da Silva from just outside the penalty area goes harmlessly over the target. </value>
<value>55:08 Giorgos Karagounis produces a right-footed shot from just outside the box that goes wide left of the target. </value>
<value>52:43 Foul by Antonio Valencia on John Arne Riise, free kick awarded. Direct free kick taken by John Arne Riise. </value>
<value>51:54 The referee blows for offside against Antonio Valencia. Indirect free kick taken by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>50:51 The referee penalises Ashkan Dejagah for handball. Wayne Rooney takes the direct free kick. </value>
<value>49:03 Rafael Da Silva gives away a free kick for an unfair challenge on John Arne Riise. Giorgos Karagounis takes the direct free kick. </value>
<value>48:37 Robin van Persie takes a shot. Mark Schwarzer makes a save. </value>
<value>47:12 Ashkan Dejagah is ruled offside. David De Gea takes the free kick. </value>
<value>46:34 Centre by Antonio Valencia. </value>
<value>46:01 Robin van Persie challenges Giorgos Karagounis unfairly and gives away a free kick. Chris Baird restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>45:01 The game restarts for the second half. </value>
<value>45:01 Substitution Aaron Hughes is brought on as a substitute for Brede Hangeland. </value>
<value>45:00 Half time The half-time whistle blows.</value> 
<value>43:13 Robin van Persie takes a shot. Save by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>42:07 The ball is delivered by Robin van Persie, John Arne Riise makes a clearance. Corner taken left-footed by Robin van Persie from the right by-line, clearance by Brede Hangeland. </value>
<value>39:41 Antonio Valencia crosses the ball. </value>
<value>38:47 Foul by Wayne Rooney on Ashkan Dejagah, free kick awarded. The free kick is swung in left-footed by Damien Duff, Jonny Evans manages to make a clearance. </value>
<value>37:40 Ashkan Dejagah fouled by Patrice Evra, the ref awards a free kick. Free kick crossed left-footed by Damien Duff from right channel, Jonny Evans makes a clearance.</value> 
<value>33:02 Luis Nani produces a curled right-footed shot from 18 yards. Blocked by Philippe Senderos. Corner taken left-footed by Robin van Persie from the right by-line, clearance made by Brede Hangeland. Jonny Evans challenges Brede Hangeland unfairly and gives away a free kick. Free kick taken by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>31:52 Wayne Rooney takes a shot. </value>
<value>29:06 Free kick awarded for an unfair challenge on Ashkan Dejagah by Luis Nani. Free kick taken by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>27:36 Centre by Damien Duff, clearance by Rio Ferdinand. </value>
<value>27:02 Inswinging corner taken by Damien Duff from the right by-line, clearance by Robin van Persie. </value>
<value>24:36 Inswinging corner taken by Wayne Rooney from the left by-line, clearance by Brede Hangeland. </value>
<value>23:44 Unfair challenge on Bryan Ruiz by Robin van Persie results in a free kick. Free kick taken by Bryan Ruiz. </value>
<value>21:55 Damien Duff gives away a free kick for an unfair challenge on Tom Cleverley. Robin van Persie delivers the ball from the free kick left-footed from right channel, clearance by Bryan Ruiz. </value>
<value>20:20 Foul by Luis Nani on Giorgos Karagounis, free kick awarded. Direct free kick taken by Chris Baird. </value>
<value>19:46 Antonio Valencia crosses the ball, blocked by John Arne Riise. </value>
<value>18:47 Wayne Rooney produces a right-footed shot from the edge of the area and misses to the left of the target. </value>
<value>18:36 Brede Hangeland gives away a free kick for an unfair challenge on Luis Nani. Patrice Evra takes the free kick. </value>
<value>15:05 Antonio Valencia produces a right-footed shot from deep inside the penalty box which goes wide of the right-hand upright.</value> 
<value>17:27 The assistant referee signals for offside against Robin van Persie. Mark Schwarzer takes the free kick. </value>
<value>17:04 Ashkan Dejagah produces a right-footed shot from the edge of the box and misses to the right of the target. </value>
<value>16:32 Bryan Ruiz fouled by Patrice Evra, the ref awards a free kick. The free kick is delivered left-footed by Bryan Ruiz from right wing, Rio Ferdinand makes a clearance. </value>
<value>15:05 Effort from inside the area by Luis Nani misses to the right of the target. </value>
<value>14:52 Corner taken right-footed by Wayne Rooney from the left by-line, Brede Hangeland manages to make a clearance. </value>
<value>14:19 Bryan Ruiz takes a shot. </value>
<value>13:51 Centre by Luis Nani, clearance made by Philippe Senderos. </value>
<value>12:09 The assistant referee signals for offside against Antonio Valencia. Mark Schwarzer takes the indirect free kick. </value>
<value>11:14 John Arne Riise has a drilled shot. Save by David De Gea. Inswinging corner taken left-footed by Damien Duff, save by David De Gea. </value>
<value>10:21 Rafael Da Silva sends in a cross, blocked by Brede Hangeland. </value>
<value>7:17 Inswinging corner taken left-footed by Robin van Persie from the right by-line, Patrice Evra takes a shot. Patrice Evra takes a shot. Save by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>7:03 The ball is sent over by Wayne Rooney. </value>
<value>6:16 Luis Nani takes a shot. Blocked by Sascha Riether. Inswinging corner taken by Wayne Rooney, Mark Schwarzer makes a save. </value>
<value>5:25 Bryan Ruiz concedes a free kick for a foul on Patrice Evra. David De Gea takes the free kick. </value>
<value>4:53 The ball is delivered by Rafael Da Silva, save by Mark Schwarzer. </value>
<value>4:00 Ashkan Dejagah takes a shot. </value>
<value>1:24 Free kick awarded for an unfair challenge on Giorgos Karagounis by Tom Cleverley. Philippe Senderos takes the free kick. </value>
<value>0:45 A cross is delivered by Luis Nani, Giorgos Karagounis gets a block in. </value>
<value>0:00 The referee gets the match started.</value>
            </list>
        </constructor-arg>
	</bean> 

	<bean id="match2" class="com.captaindebug.producerconsumer.Match">
		<constructor-arg value="Arsenal vs Stoke City" />
        <constructor-arg>
            <list>
<value>95:40 END OF FILE</value>
<value>95:22 Final Score  Arsenal 1 - 0 Stoke</value>
<value>95:21 Full time The referee blows his whistle to end the game. </value>
<value>94:06 Unfair challenge on Laurent Koscielny by Kenwyne Jones results in a free kick. Wojciech Szczesny takes the free kick. </value>
<value>92:40 Michael Owen gives away a free kick for an unfair challenge on Mikel Arteta. Direct free kick taken by Mikel Arteta. </value>
<value>89:58 Laurent Koscielny restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>89:58 Substitution Theo Walcott goes off and Aaron Ramsey comes on. </value>
<value>89:58 Nacho Monreal fouled by Cameron Jerome, the ref awards a free kick. </value>
<value>88:10 Mikel Arteta restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>88:10 Booking Ryan Shawcross is given a yellow card. </value>
<value>88:04 Free kick awarded for a foul by Ryan Shawcross on Laurent Koscielny. </value>
<value>82:39 Ryan Shawcross takes the free kick. </value>
<value>82:39 Substitution (Stoke) makes a substitution, with Michael Owen coming on for Geoff Cameron. </value>
<value>82:39 Substitution Jonathan Walters goes off and Cameron Jerome comes on. </value>
<value>82:39 Substitution Kenwyne Jones is brought on as a substitute for Peter Crouch. </value>
<value>82:39 Laurent Koscielny challenges Peter Crouch unfairly and gives away a free kick. </value>
<value>80:50 Jack Wilshere takes the inswinging corner, Ryan Shawcross manages to make a clearance. </value>
<value>79:48 Santi Cazorla takes a shot. Save by Asmir Begovic. Theo Walcott decides to take a short corner.</value> 
<value>79:41 Santi Cazorla takes a shot. Blocked by Ryan Shawcross. Santi Cazorla takes a shot. Blocked by Ryan Shawcross. </value>
<value>77:11 Assist on the goal came from Theo Walcott. </value>
<value>77:11 Goal scored. Goal - Lukas Podolski - Arsenal 1 - 0 Stoke Lukas Podolski grabs a goal direct from the free kick from just outside the area low into the middle of the goal. Arsenal 1-0 Stoke. </value>
<value>76:14 Booking Andy Wilkinson is given a yellow card.</value>
<value>75:57 Unfair challenge on Theo Walcott by Andy Wilkinson results in a free kick. </value>
<value>74:12 The assistant referee signals for offside against Peter Crouch. Laurent Koscielny restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>73:27 Shot from long distance by Nacho Monreal misses to the right of the goal. </value>
<value>71:38 Headed effort from deep inside the area by Olivier Giroud misses to the right of the goal. </value>
<value>69:42 Direct free kick taken by Jack Wilshere. </value>
<value>69:42 Booking Glenn Whelan booked for unsporting behaviour. </value>
<value>69:32 Santi Cazorla fouled by Glenn Whelan, the ref awards a free kick. </value>
<value>68:46 Bacary Sagna challenges Matthew Etherington unfairly and gives away a free kick. Free kick crossed left-footed by Matthew Etherington from left wing, clearance made by Per Mertesacker. </value>
<value>67:22 Substitution Santi Cazorla replaces Vassiriki Diaby. </value>
<value>67:22 Substitution Lukas Podolski comes on in place of Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain. </value>
<value>63:48 Ryan Shawcross has an effort at goal from just outside the area which goes wide of the left-hand post. </value>
<value>61:09 Geoff Cameron is caught offside. Laurent Koscielny takes the indirect free kick. </value>
<value>55:18 Effort on goal by Olivier Giroud from deep inside the area goes harmlessly over the bar. </value>
<value>51:04 Ryan Shotton concedes a free kick for a foul on Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain. Jack Wilshere takes the free kick.</value> 
<value>50:20 Free kick awarded for an unfair challenge on Jack Wilshere by Robert Huth. Mikel Arteta takes the direct free kick.</value> 
<value>48:59 Inswinging corner taken by Theo Walcott, Asmir Begovic makes a save. </value>
<value>46:45 Unfair challenge on Mikel Arteta by Peter Crouch results in a free kick. Mikel Arteta takes the free kick. 45:01 The referee gets the second half underway. </value>
<value>48:23 Half time</value>
<value>40:01 Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain takes a shot. Save made by Asmir Begovic. Corner from the right by-line taken by Jack Wilshere, clearance made by Steven Nzonzi. Inswinging corner taken right-footed by Theo Walcott from the left by-line, clearance by Peter Crouch. </value>
<value>38:25 Olivier Giroud is caught offside. Asmir Begovic restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>34:31 Laurent Koscielny takes a shot. Asmir Begovic makes a save. </value>
<value>33:58 Inswinging corner taken by Theo Walcott from the left by-line, Peter Crouch manages to make a clearance. </value>
<value>30:39 Corner taken by Jack Wilshere from the right by-line, Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain takes a shot. Save by Asmir Begovic. Inswinging corner taken by Theo Walcott, Peter Crouch makes a clearance. </value>
<value>29:36 Unfair challenge on Olivier Giroud by Ryan Shawcross results in a free kick. Free kick taken by Mikel Arteta. </value>
<value>29:04 Effort on goal by Ryan Shawcross from just outside the area goes harmlessly over the target. </value>
<value>25:37 Theo Walcott takes a shot. Blocked by Andy Wilkinson. Foul by Mikel Arteta on Geoff Cameron, free kick awarded. Free kick taken by Asmir Begovic. </value>
<value>22:35 Corner from the right by-line taken by Jack Wilshere, save made by Asmir Begovic. </value>
<value>21:50 Shot from just outside the box by Glenn Whelan goes over the bar. </value>
<value>20:51 Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain takes a shot. Ryan Shawcross gets a block in. Olivier Giroud is caught offside. Asmir Begovic takes the free kick. </value>
<value>17:04 Headed effort from the edge of the area by Ryan Shawcross goes wide of the right-hand post. Free kick awarded for an unfair challenge on Theo Walcott by Andy Wilkinson. Jack Wilshere crosses the ball from the free kick left-footed from right wing, Robert Huth manages to make a clearance. </value>
<value>16:33 Peter Crouch takes a shot. Laurent Koscielny gets a block in. Inswinging corner taken by Matthew Etherington. </value>
<value>14:38 Olivier Giroud produces a headed effort from deep inside the six-yard box which goes wide of the right-hand upright. </value>
<value>13:49 Jonathan Walters takes a shot. Wojciech Szczesny makes a save. </value>
<value>12:29 Free kick awarded for an unfair challenge on Theo Walcott by Matthew Etherington. Bacary Sagna takes the free kick. </value>
<value>6:15 Corner from the right by-line taken by Jack Wilshere, Geoff Cameron manages to make a clearance. Inswinging corner taken left-footed by Jack Wilshere played to the near post, Glenn Whelan manages to make a clearance. </value>
<value>4:57 Jack Wilshere takes a shot from inside the box clearing the bar. </value>
<value>1:57 Effort from the edge of the area by Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain goes wide of the left-hand upright. </value>
<value>1:06 Free kick awarded for an unfair challenge on Jack Wilshere by Geoff Cameron. Mikel Arteta restarts play with the free kick. </value>
<value>0:00 The match has kicked off.</value>
</list>
</constructor-arg>
</bean>
 
 
 
 
</beans>
